Добре дошли. Казвам се Робър Брейкър и
днес искам да ви обясня
как да бъдете спасени, какво Библията казва относно
"КАК ДА БЪДЕМ СПАСЕНИ". В Евреи 9:27 в Библията пише
"И тъй като е определено на човеците веднъж да умрат, а след това настава съд"
Всеки човек ще умре един ден. Библията
ни казва, че всеки трябва да умре, но
къде ще отидеш ти като умреш?
Ще прекараш вечността в рая или в ада?
Димящ или недимящ?
Някога мислил ли си за това?
Библията ни казва как да отидем в рая.
Казва, че трябва да бъдем спасени от ада.
Така, че да бъдеш спасен, означава, че си спасен от ада и ще отидеш в рая когато умреш.
В 1 Тимотей 2:4, Библията говори за Бог или Исус Христос:
"Който иска да се спасят всичките човеци и да достигнат до познание на истината."
"Познание на истината" означава, че има нещо, което трябва да знаеш, да чуеш, за да разбереш "КАК ДА БЪДЕШ СПАСЕН".
Така че, това което искам да направя днес е да ти дам знанието за истината и "КАК ДА БЪДЕШ СПАСЕН"
В Йоан 3:15 пише "че всеки, който вярва в Него няма да погине, но ще има вечен живот."
Бог иска да ти даде вечен живот.
Искаш ли да разбереш как да имаш вечен живот в рая?
В Деяния 13:38 пише: "Нека ви бъде известно, следователно, хора и братя, че чрез Него (Христос) се проповядва на вас прощение на греховете."
Бог предлага опрощение на всичките ти грехове
и вечен живот, но не чрез нашите дела,
а чрез Словото на Бог, което ни довежда до Исус Христос
и до това какво Той е направил за теб.
Нека първо разгледаме някои стихове в Библията относно "как да бъдем спасени".
Първо трябва да разбереш, че си грешник.
Някои хора си мислят, че са добри и че заслужават рая.
Те мислят "Толкова съм добър, че Бог трябва да ми отвори перлените врати, за да ме пусне".
Но какво казва Библията?
Казва ли Библията, че има добри хора? Хиляда пъти "НЕ!"
В Римляни 3:10 четем: "Както е писано: Няма праведни, не, ни един"
Това означава, че никой не е достатъчно добър да иде в рая.
Римляни 3:23 казва "Защото всички съгрешиха и не достигат до Божията слава"
Тъй че, без значение колко добър мислиш че си,
Бог те вижда какъвто всъщност си, Бог те вижда като грешник.
Защо умират хората? Заради греха.
Ако не беше грешник щеше да живееш вечно, но
всеки умира и, както започнахме,
"И тъй като е определено на човеците веднъж да умрат, а след това настава съд"
says it appointed unto man once to die
Когато умреш ще застанеш пред Бог да дадеш обяснение за себе си на Бог.
Римляни 5:12 пише "Затова, както чрез един човек грехът влезе в света,
и смъртта чрез греха, и така смъртта мина във ВСИЧКИТЕ човеци, понеже ВСИЧКИ съгрешиха"
Всички мъже съгрешиха, всички жени съгрешиха, когато Библията казва "всички човеци", има впредвид
всички които някога са се раждали са грешници.
Заради това умират. Така че спасението не е нещо, което може да заработим.
А е дар от Бог. Как да приемеш този дар?
Библията ни учи - ЧРЕЗ ВЯРА. Чрез вяра сме спасени.
В Ефесяни 2:8-9 пише: "Защото по благодат сте спасени чрез вяра, и то не от сами вас, а е дарът от Бог, не чрез дела, да не би някой човек да се хвали"
Спасението не е чрез това, което ние правим. Не можем да заслужим пътя си към рая,
защото не сме добри, "Няма праведни, не, ни един"
Това е дар, който Бог ни предлага. И какво представлява този дар?
В Римляни 6:23 пише: "Заплатата за греха е смърт, но дарът на Бог е вечен живот"
through Jesus Christ our Lord
so salvation is not of works but rather
receiving eternal life by faith faith is
how God chose to save us today not by
works Galatians 2:16 says knowing that a
man is not justified by the works of the
law but by the faith of Jesus Christ
even we have believed in Jesus Christ
that we might be justified by the faith
of Christ not by the works of the law
unless
by the works of the law shall no flesh
be justified you can't get to heaven by
your works God won't allow a sinner to
come in to the pearly gates
so God offers a free gift of eternal
life but that free gift is only through
faith not of works romans 4:5 says but
to him that worketh not but believeth on
him that justifieth the ungodly his
faith is counted for righteousness but
the question is faith in what the answer
is faith in the gospel the gospel is
found in first Corinthians chapter 15
and verses 1 through 4 and the gospel is
that Jesus Christ died for our sins I'll
read that to you
let me go ahead and write it up here the
gospel I hope you have a Bible and I
hope if you do you go through these
verses with me and look them up see what
the Bible says about salvation because
this is the most important thing in the
entire world
you're never dying so where you will
spend eternity for all eternity where
will your soul be for all eternity the
gospel is in 1st Corinthians chapter 15
verses 1 through 4 and as we read first
Corinthians one through four we we see
what it is that God did for us it's not
what we do that saves us it's all what
Jesus Christ did for us we read in 1st
Corinthians 15 1 through 4 moreover
moreover brethren I declare unto you the
gospel which I preached unto you which
also you received and wherein you stand
by which also ye are saved if you keep
in memory what I've preached unto you
unless you believed in vain for I
delivered unto you first of all that
which I also received how that Christ
died for our sins according to the
scriptures and that he was buried and
that he rose again the third day
according to the scriptures so the
gospel is that Jesus Christ died he died
on the cross shedding his blood on the
cross of Calvary the gospel is that he
died was buried and rose again the third
day according to the scriptures but I
left out a few words the most important
words it says for our sins why did Jesus
Christ died he died for our
sins Jesus Christ died in our place for
our sins he paid for your sins so you
don't have to go to hell and pay for
them for all eternity
so the gospel is what Jesus Christ did
for you Jesus Christ died in your place
for your sins on the cross of Calvary
paying for your sins that so that you
don't have to go to hell and pay for
them yourself
he is the sacrifice for all sinners and
his sacrifice is clearly seen when you
died on the cross the old saying is
Jesus Christ loved me this much as he
spread his arms and died in first John
4:10 we read about the love of Jesus and
his sacrifice first John 4:10 says here
in his love not that we loved God but
that he loved us and sent his son to be
the propitiation for our sins a
propitiation is like a substitute he
died in my place he paid for my sins
first John 2:2 says and not for ours
only but also for the sins of the whole
world who did Jesus Christ die for the
entire world
he paid for the sins of the entire world
1st Peter 3:18 we read for Christ also
hath once suffered for sins the just for
the unjust that he might bring us to God
being put to death in the flesh but
quickened by the spirit so Jesus Christ
died once and that one death was for our
sins
not just my sins and your sins but the
sins of the entire world
Jesus Christ died for everyone what for
the verse says that he might bring us to
God the way to heaven is through the
death burial and resurrection of Jesus
Christ
because Jesus did that for our sins and
if you come and accept the gospel and
trust the gospel it's to bring us to God
it takes us to heaven that's how we get
saved
so Jesus Christ is the one who saves and
salvation is by Jesus dying for your
sins but not only did he die how did he
die
he'd shed
blood for you it's through the blood
that Jesus Christ shed that paid for our
sins in Hebrews chapter 19 verse 22 the
Bible says and almost all things are by
the law purged with blood and without
shedding of blood is no remission of the
sins God demands blood for sins the Old
Testament God told them to sacrifice
animals and in the Old Testament those
animals were sacrificed and that
sacrifice of animals is what gave them
forgiveness of sins well now we have the
New Testament and in the New Testament
it's Jesus Christ who is our sacrifice
today we don't go and sacrifice the lamb
or an animal Jesus was the sacrifice in
fact when Jesus came John the Baptist
said behold the lamb of God which taketh
away the sin of the world that's why in
Hebrews chapter 9 and verse 12 we read
neither by the blood of goats and calves
but by his own blood he entered in once
into the holy place having obtained
eternal redemption for us Jesus died to
redeem mankind first Peter 1:18 says for
as much as you know that you were not
redeemed with corruptible things as
silver and gold from your vain
conversation received by tradition from
your father's but with the precious
blood of Christ as of a lamb without
blemish and without spot Jesus Christ
the Lamb of God died in my place for my
sins and your sins and now in the New
Testament when we build in the New
Testament it talks about Jesus Christ it
tells us that forgiveness is not from
the animals that they sacrificed under
the law salvation is not through the
blood of a goat or a lamb salvation is
through the blood shed by Jesus Christ
that's why Colossians 1:14 says and whom
we have redemption through his Jesus's
blood even the forgiveness of sins first
John 1:7 says in the blood of Jesus
Christ His Son cleanseth us from all sin
salvation is by the blood of Jesus
Christ
He shed his precious blood for you and
the question is what have you done with
Jesus Christ to be saved you must trust
that blood that Jesus said shed for you
Romans chapter 3 verses 23 through 28
are some powerful scriptures about
salvation in these passages of Romans
3:24 through 28 we read being justified
freely by His grace through the
redemption that is in Christ Jesus
salvation is by grace not by works by
believing Romans 3:25 whom God had set
forth to be a propitiation through faith
in his blood to declare his
righteousness for the remission of sins
that are past through the forbearance of
God to declare I say at this time his
righteousness that he might be just and
the justifier of him which believeth in
Jesus
where's boasting then is it is excluded
but what law works
named by the law of faith therefore we
conclude that a man is justified by
faith without the deeds of the law Jesus
Christ is the righteous who never sinned
the sinless one the just died for us the
unjust of the sinners and by so doing he
proved that he was God who died at shed
his blood and by rising again he proved
that he was gone Jesus Christ was God
manifest in the flesh that means Jesus
is God and that God loved us enough that
he died for our sins and then it says
where is boasting then it is excluded we
can't boast and say how good we are will
never compare to how good god is and how
good Jesus is so we can't boast in
ourselves and our works we have to boast
in Jesus Christ and his finished work
what he did when he died for our sins
when you come to Jesus and believe what
he's done for you and trust in the blood
you are saved and on your way to heaven
you have forgiveness of sins the Bible
says Ephesians 1:13 says in whom ye also
trusted after that ye heard the word of
truth the gospel of your salvation in
him also after that she believed you
were sealed with that holy spirit of
promise that means when you are saved
you receive the Holy Spirit you are
again salvation is so simple it's simply
trusting and believing what Jesus did
for you because he did all this for our
sins in your place for you first John
5:13 says that you can know that you're
saved it says these things have I
written unto you that believe on the
name of the Son of God that you may know
that you have eternal life and that you
may believe on the name of the Son of
God do you know that you're saved you
can what did Jesus do for you he did
everything necessary to save you he died
in your place for your sins he paid for
your sins now you can say I don't want
that and go to hell and pay for your
sins for all eternity
that's what happens if you don't accept
Jesus as your Savior or you can take the
free gift that Jesus offers of eternal
life by trusting in the gospel trusting
in his shed blood and then God saves you
and gives you eternal life believe what
Jesus did for you trust the blood
sacrifice of Jesus Christ and you'll be
saved and on your way to heaven if you
got saved watching this video I'd love
to hear from you
you can look up the website at the end
of this video and go there and find my
email address and Samiha an email let me
know this is what all of life is about
it's finding Jesus and being saved so
that you don't go to hell when you die
you go to heaven with Jesus Christ this
has been a video on how to get saved are
you saved